Welcome to Taco Par!
Yes, is this the venue?
Yes, this is the venue.
Taco Fest.
It's so unassuming.
We've spent so much time here.
I thought it'd be more luxurious.
I thought it'd be more fancy... with sparkly balloons and stuff.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm sorry, it's just so plain.
Shall we cook?
I'm aiming for a drinkable takoyaki.
This is it.
Crumbly.
You're particular, aren't you, Natsu?
She's very particular.
It has a lot of water.
I just eyeballed it.
All of it.
No hard dough, like okonomiyaki.
I make it loose, so it's more soupy.
You like soup, don't you?
I want to make enough soup to burn you. That's why I ate so much.
I want to make soup like this, so that's why I ate a lot of it.
I could swallow it without chewing it
That's right, that's right, that's right!
You don't put that much water in it?
Well, you'll have to adjust it.
I don't know the source.
I don't think I'd put that much water in.
I use takoyaki flour from the supermarket.
I think takoyaki should be crunchy.
Yeah.
The outside should be crispy.
That's true.
Yes.
That's right.
I love this whisk.
You said you were going to make omu-rice that day, but you're not going to make anything else?
I don't end up eating much food, so... but you don't make anything else? I don't end up eating much food.
I don't cook much.
That's true.
After I cook, I can make Bean-curd soup with Bean-curd soup.
Wow, that's amazing!
I can only make Bean-curd soup well.
You know, bean-curd soup with hot pepper paste...
Yeah, bean-paste, bean-paste, noodles...yeah, noodles.
I've made it on that channel.
Really?
Other than that, not so much.
But I like it. It's like an experiment.
Cooking.
I know what you mean.
Sometimes I cook because it's fun.
It's okay if you make a mistake, right?
That's right.
Like, "If I put this in, it'll be good.
"It would be softer or tougher if I added this.
Sorry about the water.
You put a lot of water in.
That much?
That's all the broth!
Soup? You want some.
I do.
I mean...
It's not sludgy at all.
Yes, it is.
It's like...
Like this?
Takoyaki.
I'll have them put oil on it.
How do you do it?
This?
Well?
Pretty good?
You want some?
No, it's fine. It's, uh, it's fine.
Wow, what a takoyaki!
I like takoyaki.
I'm glad you like it.
That's good.
Surprisingly, you don't eat takoyaki everyday.
I don't eat takoyaki.
I don't get a chance.
We have five of them.
Do you use them all at once?
Not all at once.
Depends on how many people are around.
Are you sure you want to do this?
It's fine.
Thank you.
This one right here can wait. This is cool.
Wait here, please.
Please wait.
You want to hear a lot of soup stock?
Maybe I do.
You like dashi, don't you?
Dashi is good, isn't it?
Is that...
The kind you put in miso soup?
Yes, that's right.
Downstream dashi.
Wow.
Is this it? Is it a little thick?
I'm the type who uses disposable chopsticks.
Oh, you don't use something like "nopin"?
Yes, I'm not good at it.
This one looks harder.
You must be hungry.
Takoyaki is air.
What?
Air?
What do you mean?
It's mostly air, so it won't fill you up.
That's enough of that.
Can you eat all the time?
No, really, really.
I mean, you ate 30 of them.
I ate 30 of them. They're air.
Air?
Not air? Almost.
It's a lot of powder.
I'm sure you didn't use more than 500 grams.
But it's a lot of water.
Yes, water water water.
Is there a lot of water?
Water content. It's just juice.
So will I lose weight? If you eat this.
You'll lose weight, you'll lose weight. Minus, I'll do it. There's no minus.
Let's have an octopus.
Let's talk about it.
One at a time.
No, no, no, no, I don't care where you start.
It's okay, as long as you know where you put it.
Where did you put the octopus?
When you ate 30, how many did you eat?
He didn't eat any.
No, you're too critical.
I only ate five.
No, seriously, I only ate 5.
Did you count them?
Did you count them? Did you count them?
I thought, "Oh, I only ate five.
No, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, really.
I can't weigh 130 kilograms.
Seriously? Seriously?
But you're not eating?
Are you eating?
I'm eating. I'm eating.
Really? - Yeah.
Yeah, I'm sure.
Do you really put that much in a takoyaki?
You put the juice in, you put the juice in, it's a little bit hard. Put some juice in it.
It's a little bit hard.
I'll put more water.
Still more?
I don't like this.
Want to stop?
Only in your area, Natsu.
It's too much work.
But it's nice, Natsu's area.
I'm a discolored person.
I don't want to bother people with this kind of thing.
You don't mind cheese?
I don't mind the cheese, but not all of it.
Do whatever you want?
Not even green onions.
Let's not do that.
This is Natsu's.
This is not a hole. There's no box.
I like it, but can I put it in here like this?
It's fine.
And then you put the cheese in, too.
Yeah, it's a little hard.
Is it all nuts and cheese?
Yeah, yeah.
Okay, yeah.
It's good, but...
It's hard.
Thank you.
It's better to keep it really simple.
You-know-who zone.
I'll do the same with the soup, but I don't have many ingredients.
Do you want green onions?
Yes.
Thank you.
I used to make takoyaki with my Tamagotchi.
I used to make takoyaki with Tamagotchi software.
So I'm used to making takoyaki with these onions.
I'm looking forward to it.
Mesa, it's an adjustment, so there's a chance it could go wrong.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah? - Yeah.
This place is really...
Oh, that's not good?
Hmm?
Is it hard?
It's just a little doughy, not quite moist enough.
Heh.
Let's do it.
What do you think?
Well, there's a line, like a gouge.
Yes, sir.
Just cut right here.
Cut it.
I cut it.
And when you grind it...
If the dough moves when you grind it, you can give it back.
Oh, it works?
Yeah, it's good, right?
It's hard to use chopsticks, isn't it? Oh, it works? You can do it, right?
You don't have trouble with chopsticks? What? I can't do it myself. I have to use chopsticks.
So, what's this? Like this?
Oh, that's good.
That's good.
I don't know what's going on.
It's not working. Can you go over there?
Oh, that's good. That's good.
Not chopsticks.
Not chopsticks?
They're not round at all.
If you do it with these, you'll see.
That's it.
That's good.
It's definitely easier this way.
It's easier to see.
It's beautiful.
This is a little bit undrinkable.
Not yet. Not yet?
I can't imagine what you mean by drinkable takoyaki.
It's mostly soup.
But don't you want the staff to try it?
I'm sure they'd love it.
It's good.
I'll give you the failures.
Okay, okay, okay.
I'll give you the fail.
It's like a teppanyaki.
It's like tompeyaki.
It's getting round.
It's so beautiful, isn't it?
What was your art?
What was the art?
Two?
Maybe two.
You're really good with your hands. I thought you had a good eye for art.
I don't have any.
What was it?
I got a 5.
I didn't go to school, but I got a 5 in art.
I got a 5 in art because I was allowed to make art at home and turn it in.
I was allowed to make and serve art at home, so that was part of it.
I didn't eat lunch in the classroom.
I had to eat in a weird little room.
During the time I was able to go to school, the art teacher was the only one who would come to see me.
And he was always talking to me, and we got along so well, I got a 5.
A connection? I think it was a connection.
I see.
But it's nice to have a teacher who's nice to you.
It was nice.
You got a minute? Here.
I think we're done here.
You want to do it?
Oh, my God, that looks so good.
It's got cheese in it.
Oh, no.
Hey, what's wrong?
I fell.
It's round. It's supposed to roll.
I'm talking about the shape.
It's too round.
You want to open a katsuobushi?
Yes.
We don't need all this.
Honestly.
Straight from the bone?
If not, why not?
What if it's not choku?
What about sauce? Sauce?
How do you eat it?
Tell me how to eat it.
I'm into Worcestershire sauce.
This?
Yeah.
I'm addicted to Worcestershire sauce.
You pour it on? Like this?
Yeah, like this? Yeah, I'm addicted to Worcestershire sauce. Like this?
Like this?
Like this? Yeah, like this?
Mayonnaise?
Oh, I'll just put a little bit on it for you.
Mmm-hmm.
Yes, please.
Right away.
Wow.
This is, well, orthodox for now, isn't it?
I guess this is orthodox for now.
Shall we eat then?
Let's eat.
Oh, you haven't eaten yet?
Go ahead, eat.
Bon appétit.
This is hot.
You're right, this is a little dangerous.
It smells dangerous.
Yeah!
Yum!
Yum?
That's it.
You got it?
I can drink it.
I can drink it now. That's it! Can you drink it? I can drink it! I can drink it now! Good, I can drink it now.
I can drink it. I can drink it.
Yeah, it's good.
Yum!
Yum.
Yeah! Yeah! Yum!
Hot!
You know what?
Hot.
It's got a little esophageal warmth to it, doesn't it?
It burns your throat.
Oh, I could eat for hours.
Infinite.
Endless, endless, endless.
Infinity, infinity, infinity.
No, I can still drink this.
I could go on.
Still got it.
I thought it was enough.
I'm not done yet.
I'd like to keep going until the very last minute.
But won't that make it harder? This baking...
It's hard.
It's hard, but you want to drink it.
I can drink this, but it's a little sticky.
But it's really thick.
You see how liquidy it is?
It's not even half-raw, it's raw.
No, it's not raw.
Oh, it's not raw? Raw? It's not raw.
It's not raw. It's okay, it's okay. You see the amounts on the back?
Flour, takoyaki flour... I use 1.5 to 1.8 times this amount of water.
But it's true.
But it's really by eye, you know, like you lift up this ladle and you see how thin the dough is.
I don't think it's easy for an amateur to imitate.
How did you come up with this recipe?
Do you put a lot of water in it?
I've been making takoyaki 3 times a week for about a year now.
Oh no!
I've been making takoyaki for about a year now.
All the time.
Takoyaki takoyaki, please.
It's a life of takoyaki
A life of takoyaki.
I used to do takoyaki all the time.
I hope you understand.
Takopa.
People love takoyaki.
I don't really eat takoyaki outside.
You don't eat takoyaki for lunch.
Takoyaki, yes.
Especially when they're hot.
Look, look, I don't know.
I don't know.
It's an odd one, but there are other ones.
I don't know, I don't know.
You want to try something different? I just did an orthodox one.
I'll do it.
Mentaiko.
Umeboshi.
It's so good.
Warm pickled plums are so good.
Really?
Please, please.
What are these? Mochi mochi mochi.
Put it in! Put it in any way you want.
Now, now, now. Is it too late?
No, it's okay. It's okay.
Dried plums?
One plum is a bit much, so just tear it up.
I like a little bit. I like a little bit.
A little bit.
Dried plums are really good.
Delicious.
Yum.
Mentaiko.
Mentaiko. I love mentaiko.
It's delicious.
How's the takuan?
It's really good.
I love takuan.
Put it in, it's really good.
This sour stuff goes well with it.
I don't know which one I put in which one.
You're right.
I don't know which one I put in which one. I don't know which one I put in which one, but sure.
I don't know which ones I put in which ones.
Sure, put them in.
Can we have rice cakes?
What about the rice cakes?
Which one do we put it in? I don't have any more.
Sausage?
Sausage.
Yes, fish sausage. It's like an American dog.
With ketchup.
You eat ketchup with fish sausage?
With fish sausage.
You see how it's looser?
It's more watery.
Like the Nakagawa family in Osaka.
Or Kanpei's in Osaka.
I went to make takoyaki.
Yeah.
It's on the show.
What do you mean? Like...
Reverse?
Like a reverse import.
How do people in Osaka react when they eat it?
They said it's really good.
Very good.
Like Mr. Kawashima from Kirin.
There must have been 10 people there.
We grilled from 4:00 to 3:00 a.m.
Amazing!
So you have all the ingredients to make takoyaki at home?
Yes, we always have inferior octopus.
Flour is always available.
So it's like that.
I can make takoyaki as soon as I feel like it.
Do you sometimes make takoyaki for yourself?
Yes, I do.
I have one for one person. It's a 6-hole.
Six holes?
For one person.
Why don't you open a store?
That's not it.
Not that one. Not that one.
How often do you open a restaurant?
I want to cook at home, like this.
It's a different level when it's a restaurant.
Selling and putting things up.
The people at the store are amazing.
Takoyaki is great.
You lose track of time.
You're the only one who makes them, but this is great.
Yeah?
It's kind of scary making takoyaki by yourself.
It's a little... well, cloak-and-dagger.
That's true.
You don't have a boyfriend?
Do you have one?
No, I don't.
I want one.
You want one?
What kind of man do you like?
What do you mean, someone you can talk to? What do you mean, someone you can talk to? What kind of person do you like?
Someone I can talk to.
What do you mean? Someone who can talk?
Someone who can talk.
Oh, that's right.
Well, yes.
Someone you can talk to?
Yes, I do.
Someone fun to be with.
Yeah. - Yeah.
I don't care what they look like.
Yeah, they're all different.
Ever?
What have they been like?
They're all different.
Soy sauce, salt, and pepper.
No one really looks like anyone else.
Soy sauce, salt and pepper sauce.
Osaka takoyaki
Soy sauce salt sauce Osaka takoyaki!
Soy sauce, salt sauce...
Is it done?
It's ready.
It's good with yuzu kosho, too. Salt.
Salt is good. Salt is good.
I like salt.
Yuzu kosho is so good... and yuzu kosho... and yuzu... and now we have sweets.
Natto (fermented soybeans)...
I'm going to go into varieties.
I really don't need natto.
Crab cakes, raisins...
I don't want raisins.
Chocolate raisins.
I don't want chocolate raisins.
I can't eat raisins.
I don't want marshmallows.
No.
Salted fish.
Wait a minute, why don't you tell me, dog, why don't you have marshmallows? Oh, no, I don't want the salted fish.
Wait a minute, why don't you tell me what you want?
I'm saying what I want.
Say it the other way around.
I want the ones you have.
Chocolate.
If it's chocolate, I think only chocolate is good.
Only chocolate is good.
Chocolate and marshmallows?
I don't know.
I don't know... chocolate and natto?
Natto sounds bad.
I like natto.
Kimchi natto is good.
Not so good.
What?
I love spicy kimchi.
But this time, I can't eat Chinese cabbage.
What?
I can't have vegetables with a core, and I can't have vegetables with a core.
But you don't mind the leaves?
The leaves are fine.
The core is good. It's so sweet.
I can't eat it.
You can't eat it?
It's hard... to live.
It's not such a hardship.
Eat whatever you like.
No kimchi?
The leaves.
No?
Not the leafy part.
Kimchi.
Too small.
What's the point? That's it.
Let's put carrots in there too, for good luck.
Yeah, let's do it.
Chocolate?
Great. Great.
Yes, yes, yes.
Chocolate?
I'll make a chocolate zone.
Sweets.
That's right.
Chocolate, seriously.
So much chocolate!
You can try the others.
Raisins? Bananas?
Nachi told me to put in what you want to eat.
He scolded me.
I don't eat bananas.
Then I'll put raisins in it.
Raisins?
Chocolate banana raisin? Okay, let's make it a little more eye-candy and make it chocolate banana raisin.
Chocolate banana raisin.
You're a little off. Why?
Hey, you're not?
Oh, my God, that's amazing.
What?
No, there's more than that.
Let's eat this.
It's burning.
Wait, you're not eating this.
You're right, I haven't.
You have to eat it.
You can drink more than you did before.
Oh, no!
It's not going to keep the heat in.
Wow, it's so smooth.
It's delicious.
I don't know what I put in it.
You don't know?
It's hot.
Mochi?
Salt is good.
Salty, salty, salty, salty, salty.
How do you like it?
How about water and pepper?
What? What is this?
It's cod roe. Yum!
There were two octopuses.
How sad.
It was a jackpot.
It was a bit of a disappointment.
We hit the jackpot.
Really?
I wish I could say it was cod roe. Or maybe it was pickled radish.
Hmm? What? I want to say it was pickled radish.
Takuan.
Takuan (pickled radish) is good.
I can drink more than before.
I can drink it.
Takuan!
Ummm...
Ume Ume!
Sorry. Sorry.
It was a fluke.
It's not like that.
That was embarrassing.
Isn't it good?
It's delicious.
I like umeboshi.
I wonder if it goes well with pickles.
I thought kimchi and pickles would go well with it.
Surprising.
Kimchi and takuan go well together.
And takuan goes well with iburi gakko.
What's that?
Like smoked takuan.
I don't know.
So Natsu-san is kind.
Oh, no...
No, no, no, no, wait a minute.
No, no, no...
You're going to apologize to him, right?
No.
You don't know what you're talking about.
You're laughing.
Now...
I'm suddenly...
Why do you think I'm being so nice?
You'd apologize if we fought like that.
Well, I mean, I apologize, but...
But aren't there times when you don't want to apologize anymore? I don't care if we're friends or not.
I just need to cool down.
I'll leave you alone for a while.
Oh, wow.
Natsu, seriously, the guy I know... he's a really sweet guy.
Really? Is she nice?
I don't know.
I think she's a little too nice and hurtful.
I think she apologizes for things she doesn't need to apologize for.
I think he's patient.
I might endure.
You seem patient.
I do.
How did you know?
The type that can't say.
I get it, I get it, I get it.
I get it.
I suppress it.
If I could just hold it in.
I'd like to.
Self-sacrificing.
What should I do?
I think you should take care of yourself.
How can I do that?
I think you should just keep it the way it is, and be mindful of how you're feeling.
Even if you don't change your mind at all.
I think you should love whoever loves you.
Yeah.
If you have to put up with something to make it go away...
They're the selfish type, aren't they? That's exactly right.
That's for sure.
I don't think you should be with someone like that.
You're right, I shouldn't be with someone like that.
Yeah.
I like considerate people.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Try to put yourself in the other person's shoes.
Yeah.
We're strangers now.
It's like a simulation.
Not that it's the right answer.
But...
But it's good to have that attitude.
Someone who can talk things out.
Someone who can talk things through.
That's right.
Surprisingly few people are like that.
Not many.
They scare me.
That's why I don't feel like talking.
I get it.
I think anyone who makes you feel uncomfortable is a jerk.
What's going on with you?
You need to talk to her.
You have to talk to her.
I think people who do things that they're insecure or they don't like.
I think they're scum.
I don't think you can talk to them.
People who make you feel insecure are really...
You're right.
Maybe I don't like it.
If I don't tell them this, they'll get anxious.
You don't have compassion.
I see people who are insecure or jealous.
There are people who have a bad habit of seeing people as insecure or jealous.
Yes, there are.
They probably don't have confidence in themselves.
That's why they're jealous.
They want to be reassured that they're loved.
But that kind of confirmation...
You're just hurting the other person.
You're testing them.
It's not good.
I want someone I can talk to.
Are you one of those people who can't tolerate cheating?
If you're going to cheat, go there.
Yeah, right.
I'd rather she find out.
I'd rather you keep it under wraps.
You know how often that happens.
If you're going to cheat on me, you have to hide it.
You can't hide it.
I don't know about Shobokan.
But you'll know right away, won't you?
She will.
She's like, "What's wrong with that? Like that.
It just doesn't add up? Or can you tell by the color of her face or the way she looks over there?
It just doesn't add up.
Huh? You were saying this the other day. What's that? I don't know.
I don't know, I don't remember...
I don't have a memory, so I don't have a memory.
I have no memory.
Maybe it doesn't matter what he was doing or what he was doing.
That's good to know.
You're okay with the affair.
No, I'm not okay with cheating.
I don't want him to cheat on me.
I don't know what to do.
You don't have to.
It's so simple.
It's not about hiding it.
It's not about hiding.
You don't have to cheat on your wife.
If you're going to cheat on me, why don't you just go that way?
It's so boring.
It's tedious.
I'm not tired.
I don't know, I don't know, I don't know what that's like.
I don't know what you're going through, but I don't know what I'm going through at this hour.
I've been thinking about it for a long time, but then I think, well, I don't know about that experience, but I think, well, anything I say at this hour fits...
I think...
I've been thinking...
Well, then...
Sweets Takoyaki?
I'm thinking more like natto kimchi.
That looks super sweet.
Are you saying it's black with chocolate? Looks like...
Chocolate.
Well, I'll just eat it... and the kimchi.
Kimchi, then.
Okay.
I bet it's hot.
I'm sure.
Let's have natto kimchi.
Natto kimchi.
Oh, man.
It's so bad, for sure!
Oh, yum!
Kimchi? It's good, isn't it?
It's delicious.
It smells like natto.
Is it good natto?
It's good.
Yes, the smell of natto is amazing!
It's delicious!
It's bright red and also tasty. It's delicious.
It's delicious.
If the two of you could do something together again in the future, is there anything you'd like to do?
What do you mean?
Finding Mr. Natsu's girlfriend.
Ai Seat Liquor Bar?
Ai Seshoku Yakka.
Would you go look for her? Or you can call out to her at the lamppost.
A lamppost? You mean like a street record? Seriously? How long would that take?
Is there something you want to do? But like you said, we'll take the Starbike.
Wouldn't an amusement park be nice? Yeah, that's a good idea.
You like screaming, right? I like screaming.
Amusement parks are good, too. You like amusement parks, don't you?
Amusement parks are nice.
I like amusement parks.
I had a lot of delicious takoyaki today.
That's good.
How was it? Natsu!
It was a lot of fun.
Really?
Yeah, really.
It was great.
You said it was a drinking party.
Yeah.
You know, when we're having a drink, we just end up doing this, but...
I feel like we were able to have a good talk.
I'm really glad I got to know you.
Next time, let's go to an amusement park and look for a girlfriend.
Thank you very much and please subscribe to our channel!